Student10001 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 5100
Student10002 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 5100
Student10003 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 5100
Student10004 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6105
Student10005 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6105
Student10006 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6105
Student10007 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6105
Student10008 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6150
Student10009 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6150
Student10010 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6150
Student20001 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7150
Student20002 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7150
Student20003 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7210
Student20004 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7210
Student20005 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7210
Student20006 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7210
Student20007 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7250
Student20008 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7250
Student20009 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7250
Student20010 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 7250
Student30001 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6200
Student30002 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6200
Student30003 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6200
Student30004 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6205
Student30005 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6205
Student30006 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6205
Student30007 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6250
Student30008 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6250
Student30009 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6250
Student30010 was found
This is first time student is registering... creating new section in transcript.
Congrats, you are registered for 6250
CollegeNEU - College of engineering
---------------------------------------
List of programs:
DepartmentMGEN
DegreeMS in Information Systems
-------------------------------------
Course catalog:
5100 - Application Engineer - 4 - credit hours
6105 - Data Engineer with Python - 4 - credit hours
6150 - Web development - 4 - credit hours
-------------------------------------
List of Semester
Spring 2023 semester: These courses are available
 - 5100 - Application Engineer - 47 avail. out of 50total.
 - 6105 - Data Engineer with Python - 26 avail. out of 30total.
 - 6150 - Web development - 22 avail. out of 25total.
Student List
Student id10001
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Application Engineer 5100 - 0.0
Student id10002
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Application Engineer 5100 - 0.0
Student id10003
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Application Engineer 5100 - 0.0
Student id10004
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data Engineer with Python 6105 - 0.0
Student id10005
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data Engineer with Python 6105 - 0.0
Student id10006
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data Engineer with Python 6105 - 0.0
Student id10007
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data Engineer with Python 6105 - 0.0
Student id10008
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Web development 6150 - 0.0
Student id10009
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Web development 6150 - 0.0
Student id10010
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Web development 6150 - 0.0
DepartmentDAMG
DegreeData engineering degree
-------------------------------------
Course catalog:
7150 - Data management - 4 - credit hours
7210 - Data Management and Database Design - 4 - credit hours
7250 - Big Data Architecture and Governance - 4 - credit hours
-------------------------------------
List of Semester
Spring 2023 semester: These courses are available
 - 7150 - Data management - 38 avail. out of 40total.
 - 7210 - Data Management and Database Design - 26 avail. out of 30total.
 - 7250 - Big Data Architecture and Governance - 16 avail. out of 20total.
Student List
Student id20001
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data management 7150 - 0.0
Student id20002
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data management 7150 - 0.0
Student id20003
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data Management and Database Design 7210 - 0.0
Student id20004
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data Management and Database Design 7210 - 0.0
Student id20005
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data Management and Database Design 7210 - 0.0
Student id20006
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Data Management and Database Design 7210 - 0.0
Student id20007
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Big Data Architecture and Governance 7250 - 0.0
Student id20008
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Big Data Architecture and Governance 7250 - 0.0
Student id20009
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Big Data Architecture and Governance 7250 - 0.0
Student id20010
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Big Data Architecture and Governance 7250 - 0.0
DepartmentCSYE
DegreeSoftware engineering systems
-------------------------------------
Course catalog:
6200 - Concepts of Object-Oriented Design - 4 - credit hours
6205 - Program Structure and Algorithms - 4 - credit hours
6250 - Web Development Tools and Methods - 4 - credit hours
-------------------------------------
List of Semester
Spring 2023 semester: These courses are available
 - 6200 - Concepts of Object-Oriented Design - 32 avail. out of 35total.
 - 6205 - Program Structure and Algorithms - 27 avail. out of 30total.
 - 6250 - Web Development Tools and Methods - 16 avail. out of 20total.
Student List
Student id30001
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Concepts of Object-Oriented Design 6200 - 0.0
Student id30002
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Concepts of Object-Oriented Design 6200 - 0.0
Student id30003
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Concepts of Object-Oriented Design 6200 - 0.0
Student id30004
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Program Structure and Algorithms 6205 - 0.0
Student id30005
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Program Structure and Algorithms 6205 - 0.0
Student id30006
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Program Structure and Algorithms 6205 - 0.0
Student id30007
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Web Development Tools and Methods 6250 - 0.0
Student id30008
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Web Development Tools and Methods 6250 - 0.0
Student id30009
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Web Development Tools and Methods 6250 - 0.0
Student id30010
Taking courses for semester:Spring 2023 semester
 - Web Development Tools and Methods 6250 - 0.0
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~
-------------------------------------
Application Engineer: 18000
Data Engineer with Python: 24000
Web development: 18000
Revenue for MGEN during Spring 2023 semester:60000
***********************************************
Data management: 12000
Data Management and Database Design: 24000
Big Data Architecture and Governance: 24000
Revenue for DAMG during Spring 2023 semester:60000
***********************************************
Concepts of Object-Oriented Design: 18000
Program Structure and Algorithms: 18000
Web Development Tools and Methods: 24000
Revenue for CSYE during Spring 2023 semester:60000
***********************************************
Total revenue 180000
